question_data =[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Furby was released in 1998.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"There are 86400 seconds in a day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]